[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
Previously on Dating Alys Perez.
Don't worry, okay?
After this,
I'll be gone, too.
Zy, please.
You're going over
the speed limit, Zy.
- Please!
- I don't care!
Please, listen to me!
If you have a problem,
we can talk about it, please!
Just stop the car, Zy, please!
Please, Zy!
Help!
Tripp!
Alys?
Andy...
Alys is too vulnerable.
She has been through a lot lately.
I don’t know if she can still endure this.
I don’t want her to go spiral.
Why is this happening to her?
How are we going to tell her?
Mom?
Alys!
Finally, you're awake!
Are you okay?
I mean, do you feel hurt?
Is there any pain?
Tell me!
Mommy's going to take care of you.
Mom, I can't move.
It hurts.
Don't move just yet, okay?
Baby, you're injured.
Focus on getting well.
Then we will tell you everything
when you get better.
Okay?
Zy!
Help!
Mom, where's Tripp?
Where's Tripp?
Is he okay?!
- Tell me.
- Alys...
- Mom, Mom.
- Not right now...
Not right now, dear.
I need to know!
No, no, no...
- Mommy, where's Tripp?
- Focus on getting better, okay?
Listen to us.
- Okay?
- No!
No! No, Mommy.
Please tell me where Tripp is.
- That's all I need to know.
- Alys...
I just wanna know if he's okay.
I just want to see him.
Just for a bit, Mommy.
I promise I won't cry anymore.
Please, Mommy.
I just wanna see Tripp.
Doc, is it possible to calm her down?
What happened to him?
Why aren't you answering me?
No.
She's hurting.
Why aren't you answering?
Where is he?
- Sweetie...
- Tell me, Mommy.
- Shhh...
- Mommy, no!
No, Mommy!
Tell me what happened!
Please, Please!
No, please!
Mommy!
Where is Alys Perez?
What room is she in?
Calm down, Sir.
I need to see my wife!
I'll need an ID so we can verify
and give you a visitor's pass.
Sir!
Uncle!
Drake.
Where is Alys?
I want to see her, please.
She's inside.
Go ahead.
- Auntie.
- Drake.
She's stable now.
We even asked the doctor
earlier to sedate her.
Because she was so restless
earlier when she woke up.
She'll be fine.
She's in good hands here, Drake.
Alys...
I think you have to check on Tripp,
see how he's doing.
Tripp?
Alys was with Tripp when it happened.
Alys was driving his car.
And I was told that they
came from Cristine's house.
How are you?
Are you blaming yourself?
Don't.
No one wanted this to happen.
It’s nobody's fault.
Things happen.
But why Alys?
Why Tripp?
That’s what we don’t know.
All we can do now
is pray.
And wait until they get better.
Don't worry.
They’ll be well taken care of here.
Thank goodness Bestie
wasn’t seriously hurt, right?
Seriously?
That's a tactless thing to say, you know.
What should I say instead?
I’m sorry.
You know I have no finesse
when it comes to talking.
All I’m saying is,
I'm so happy Alys is alive.
She’s okay, even if—
Bestie?
Hey, Bestie!
It's Aya!
I'm here with Sheen.
Can you see us, Bestie?
- Of course she can see us!
- Ouch!
She isn't blind, you know.
Come on, Aya.
No!
I meant if she can see us
clearly or even recognize us.
Come on.
You didn’t have to hit me that hard.
Aya. Sheen.
Bestie!
Ouch!
Good grief, Aya!
Just don't touch her, please.
- I’m sorry, Bestie.
- Are you okay?
Don't touch her.
You okay?
Promise?
Sorry for taking so long to visit, Bestie.
Your mom wouldn't let us
see you until you got better.
How are you?
You know, Bestie?
I'm glad.
I'm glad to see you doing better.
Have you been able to eat again?
Also Bestie, we got you some fruits,
cupcakes,
donuts,
and other tasty food.
If there’s anything else you’re craving,
just let me know.
Aya's overdoing it as always.
It’s as if there's a feeding
program in the hospital.
What's your problem?
This is a good thing.
Even the nurses and staff
taking care of her get to eat, too.
The food is for everybody.
You've always been
such a buzzkill, CB.
Hey!
Would you stop calling me that?
I'm not a crybaby anymore.
- Really?
- Life has made me stronger.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Whatever you say.
Why? You’ve never cried before?
In my mind,
- you'll always be a crybaby.
- No!
You've never cried then?
- Whatever!
- I didn’t cry!
Need I remind you of
our high school days?
Have you never been
heartbroken before?
Don't remind me of highschool.
- We don't have to go that far back.
- Such a crybaby!
I'm no crybaby.
- I’m not a crybaby!
- Aya!
Bestie?
Do you need anything?
How's Tripp?
Oh!
Uhh...
He's doing fine, Bestie.
He's recovering, just like you.
He's well taken care of.
Bestie,
there's no need to worry about Tripp.
What matters is that
you're both doing well,
and recovering.
You need to get stronger.
Focus on yourself, okay?
Knowing how much
you worry about others
and take care of the people you love.
You’ll be able to do all that
once you’re better.
Get better.
And with that...
Sheen and I have to go.
- Right?
- What?
Oh yeah.
Just focus on getting better.
Okay?
Aya and I just came by to
see how you were doing.
To check up on Tripp too, right?
Don't strain yourself, Alys.
Promise?
Regain your strength and recover.
We’re here for you.
Alright, Bestie.
You need to rest.
Get better and stronger.
If you want anything to eat,
let your mom know.
And I'll bring it to you when I come back.
Bestie,
Get well.
We're right here, okay?
Let’s go.
Come on.
Bye, Alys.
Where’s Tripp?
I know they’re lying about Tripp.
Drake.
How's my wife?
It's fine. I'm here.
I'm not leaving you.
Drake, where is Tripp?
Are you hungry?
Do you need anything?
Drake, where is Tripp?
Your mom brought
Arroz Caldo earlier.
She asked me to feed
you when you wake up.
You want some?
Drake.
Please tell me. Where is Tripp?
Oh, a sponge bath.
Wait, I'll call the nurse.
Drake!
Auntie.
We'll handle this.
Go home and rest, okay?
But what about Alys?
Drake, I insist.
You’ll end up getting sick
if you keep this up.
You'll wind up in a hospital bed too.
Okay.
Okay?
I'll come back tomorrow, Auntie.
Alright, get some sleep.
I'll be back tomorrow, okay, Alys?
Alys.
- Baby?
- Mom?
Mom, where is Tripp?
Why aren't you answering me?
Why won't you answer me?
I'm just asking a question.
Where is he?
Is he dead? Is he alive?
I don't know anything!
Mommy!
Where is Tripp, please?
Let me know, Mom!
Excuse me, Sir.
Thank you.
Eat, Alys.
If you keep this up, you’re going
to lose those adorable cheeks.
That’s one of the things I fell for.
Here.
How's Tripp?
Eat up, Alys.
Even just one bite.
When you're strong enough,
I'll take you to Tripp myself.
Come on.
Is she better now?
Getting better.
Recovering.
I'm sorry, Cous.
But you have to go through this.
I know you're closer to Tripp.
But I appreciate that.
Come on.
Tripp and I love you.
We're here for you.
How's Tripp?
Any news?
Well...
Auntie came.
She's not happy.
She's blaming her—
I'll try to talk to her.
Tripp.
Oh, baby Alys.
You know what your dad did the other day?
He tried to cook soup!
It's so salty!
But I still finished it.
It wasn't salty.
Huh?
Don't try to defend it.
It’s really salty.
Anyways, do you know?
Your aunts miss you so much.
Then they asked me when you'll be home.
I told them, very soon.
Then there's Aya,
she was a bit angry.
She told me that when you go out,
she'll be the first one
to take you to the spa
because she said
your life is too stressful.
Then, your nanny!
She's excited to see you.
- When you get home—
- Auntie, Uncle!
Oh, Drake!
Hello.
Where can I put this, Auntie?
Oh, let me.
Oh, were you able to sleep?
Barely.
It's obvious from your eyes.
Have you eaten?
Not yet, I was hoping Alys
and I would eat together.
Oh, you know what?
The flowers can wait.
Uh, we'll leave you with Baby Alys.
Baby Alys!
Daddy and I have to go outside.
We'll be back.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Uncle.
Alys.
What?
I brought you something.
Do you remember this?
This was the first food
we shared together at SCA.
This is good.
Eat up so you can get your
strength back and recover.
Where's Tripp? Bring me to him.
Come on, Alys.
Take me to Tripp!
Are you deaf or what?!
I just want to see Tripp.
I just want to make sure he's okay.
Drake, please.
Even for just 10 seconds.
I just want to see Tripp.
Drake!
Alys...
Even if I wanted to..
What?
You wish you can, but you can't?
Just this once, Drake.
Stand your ground for once!
You're a fucking man!
You're a grown man!
Act like it!
Go to fucking Fier!
You got Fier pregnant, right?
Take some goddamn responsibility.
Did you know I tried so hard
to keep her from leaving?
Hmm?
So hard.
Why?
Why did I do it?
Because I knew it was hard on you!
You're so stupid, Alys.
You're so goddamn stupid, Alys.
Do you know how much
I changed for you?
Because I loved you so much, Drake?
Go ahead, Alys.
Go ahead!
You can do it.
You'll just have to swallow
your pride for Drake.
Fuck.
I was so pathetic, wasn't I?
But that's okay.
I'm not blaming you for that.
It was my choice.
I chose to be stupid.
I'm just letting it all out now.
Because it hurts so much
and I'm so tired of you, Drake.
After everything I've done for you,
this is the least you can do for me.
And you can’t even grant
me this one request?!
Take me to Tripp.
If you have some pity for me, please.
Do you really want me to go crazy?
Bring me to Tripp
if you don't want me to go crazy, Drake.
Alys.
Please, Drake.
I need to see Tripp.
Alys, you can’t see Tripp.
Why?
Alys.
Alys!
Let's go.
Alys, let's go.
Tripp!
What is that woman doing here?
You have some nerve!
Get her away from me before
I start making a scene.
Okay, Auntie.
Let's go.
Drake, no!
No, please!
I want to see Tripp even for a moment.
Please, Drake.
Drake, please.
I'm begging you.
Please.
That's all I want.
Alys, listen to me.
Please.
That's Tripp's mom.
Don't visit him anymore.
Auntie is really mad at you.
But I didn’t want that to happen, Drake.
I know.
We know that.
Tell her I'm very sorry.
Please tell her.
Please tell her I didn't mean
for any of this to happen.
Please tell her.
How dare you!
I left with my son healthy.
And now I returned.
And now he's in a coma
with multiple internal injuries?
How dare you!
I'm very sorry.
I really didn't mean
for anything to happen.
I'm very sorry.
You do not deserve to see my son!
I know.
But just give me a
moment with him, please!
Even just for a moment,
I just want to see Tripp.
Please.
You almost killed him.
You almost killed my son!
And you killed your own baby?
What kind of mother are you?!
What do you mean?
My own baby?
Uh...
Is it true, Drake?
Is it true?!
Drake...
Drake, I'm so sorry.
I didn't know that she didn't know.
I didn't mean it to come from me.
You two need to talk, okay?
Drake.
Alys.
you were a few weeks pregnant.
The accident led to a miscarriage.
I hate you!
Alys, I'm sorry.
Leave me alone.
I don't want to see you, Drake.
Alys, I'm hurting too.
Let me grieve with you.
Grieve with me?
Bullshit.
Do you know what's the root of all this?
My fucking love for you, Drake.
And I always lose something
whenever I choose you.
I don't want you in my life anymore.
So please...
please just go.
Just...
leave.
Alys, please.
You've hurt me so much, Drake.
I've had enough of this.
Alys, please.
I'm so tired, Drake.
I'm so tired of you.
I'm giving up on you.
Let's end this.
Okay, the bills are paid.
Are we forgetting anything?
Ma'am, here's the copy of receipt.
Oh, thank you.
Are we ready to go?
Yeah, just give us five more minutes.
Okay, sure ma'am.
Okay, thank you.
Ready to go home, dear?
I'm so excited you're
coming home with us today.
Dane is waiting for you.
I already cleaned your room.
Your sheets are fresh.
Of course, I want you
to feel rested at home.
Aren't you excited?
Sorry, Mom.
But I'll stay at the condo for now.
Huh?
But why?
I just want to process things first.
A lot has happened.
I know, but don't you think we'll be
able to take care of you better at home?
Come on, Dad.
I'm not a kid anymore.
I can handle myself.
I almost became a mother.
Even if I found out from
someone else.
Look, Mom, Dad.
I understand the concern.
I truly do.
I get why you withheld so many truths
within a span of weeks, but
that doesn't mean I can't get hurt, right?
We understand.
But are you sure you can manage?
Yes, Mom.
I can manage.
And plus, the hospital
is closer to my condo.
So, I can visit Tripp easily.
Can I please send the nanny with you?
So you'll have someone
to clean and cook for you.
No need, Mom.
- Perez!
- Bestie!
Hey.
What happened?
I killed my baby.
Hey, this is my favorite.
Look at this.
You didn't even use a serving spoon.
Eat all of that.
Eat!
Didn't know you were this sensitive.
Huh?
Isn't that basic knowledge?
It'll go bad faster
without a serving spoon.
It won't go bad.
We'll finish this tonight!
It's not even enough
for us three, right Alys?
Can ice cream really help with sadness?
Why?
Are you sad?
A little.
But I'm not as sad as Alys.
So, Kent and you had a fight, right?
Hmm... you're a little gossip, aren't you?
How did you know?
And what's it to you?
You're more invested in
my love life than I am.
I heard that you don't have a girlfriend.
Why don't you find someone so
you don't meddle with any of ours?
So, Bestie?
Do you want to do anything tonight?
Movie marathon?
Board games?
Sound trip?
Karaoke?
I know you'll love this.
Let's grab a drink!
Oh god.
Can we not go drinking?
She's recovering.
Something might happen to her again.
Oh, right.
Sorry, not today.
Whatever it is, Alys, we got you.
Of course!
Over.
Thank you.
So unfair.
You're still handsome as ever.
You promised me, right?
You said we're soulmates.
And soulmates don't leave each other.
You said you'll help me with everything.
Just this once, please, Tripp.
Just help me with this.
Keep fighting, okay?
You can't die on me.
You can't.
I won't allow it.
You can't leave me.
Miss Alys, time's up.
Let's go.
Let's go please.
I'll come back for you, okay?
Okay.
See you.
Alys, I brought you some
flowers and some food.
Let's eat.
Drake, what else do I have to do
to make you stop?
We've been over for two months now.
We broke up already.
What else do you want?
Alys.
Here we go again.
What else do you want?!
Drake, why won't you let me go?!
Let me go!
Go away!
- Alys...
- Leave!
Don't fucking touch me!
Don't touch me!
Leave.
I said leave!
Stop waiting for someone who's
already waiting for someone else.
Save yourself, Drake.
That's enough.
Have pity on yourself.
Let's end this.
Not a single day has passed where I haven't
blamed myself for what happened.
Please wake up, Tripp.
There's so much I have
to make up to you.
Tripp, please wake up.
I'll make it up to you, I promise.
You won't be sad ever again.
You'll see, we'll just be happy.
Why is all of this happening to me?
To the people close to me.
Am I cursed?
Am I the worst person in the world
for fate to punish me like this?
Drake.
Fier.
Thank God you called.
Where are you?
I heard about what happened.
So I decided to call.
Thank you.
May I know where you are right now?
For now, not yet.
I'm not the one you
should be worried about.
I just wanted to apologize for everything.
I had to leave for my own sanity.
Everything was getting too much and
everything was out of control.
And I think everybody just
needs a little breathing.
And I just needed to be alone.
But...
what about...
who will take care of the baby?
I'll be fine.
I'll focus on myself.
And you should too.
Fix your situation with Alys.
I know that she's your real love.
Despite giving us a shot,
you didn't choose me.
You didn't choose us.
Fier.
If you need anything,
just tell me, okay?
At this moment?
Nothing.
Just let me be.
Don't worry about me.
About us.
We're fine.
Don't beat yourself up, Drake.
I know how hard it is
for you right now.
Especially with what happened to Alys.
That's why I won't
add to your burden.
For now, focus on her.
She needs you more.
But...
Relax, Drake.
I can think clearly if I'm
away from all this chaos.
Who knows?
Maybe one day,
I'll let you know where we'll be.
But for now,
take care.
I hope Alys will get better.
Thank you, Fier.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Alys.
I cooked all your favorite food.
That's why you need to eat a lot.
You don't know how
happy your mom was
when she found out you'll drop by.
Now I'm starting to believe
you are her favorite child.
Mom, I'm going back to the shop.
Huh?
Are you sure you're okay?
I mean, no one's rushing you.
You can take all the time that you need.
I just thought, it's better
if I do something than...
You know what?
Whatever you need, honey.
Your Dad and I
will always be here.
Alys, we will never get
tired of supporting you.
Remember that.
Thank you, Dad.
Thank you, Mom.
Okay, let's eat.
Nanny?
Yes, Ma'am?
I put the dessert in the freezer.
Don't forget, okay?
It's frozen.
Yes, Ma'am.
Okay, thank you.
I’ll check, thank you.
You know what, honey?
I'm so glad you're home.
You sure you don't want
to come back here?
I promise I won't fight you again.
I'm okay.
Don't worry.
You sure?
If Drake is bothering you,
just let me know.
Oh, my god.
What's wrong?
Mom, Dad, I need to go.
Where are you going?
Tofer just texted me.
I need to go to the hospital.
It's pretty urgent.
Can you please finish your food first?
Eat some more.
- Ma'am Kat.
- Yes?
Where's the patient?
Weren’t you informed?
About what?
Sir is gone.
Sorry, Ma'am.
Okay.
See you.
I'll see you tomorrow, my son.
I gotta go.
Hello, cousin.
I'm here to wish you well.
People have always
compared us to each other.
They even pit us against
each other sometimes.
But I never took it seriously.
I don't know why we weren't close.
We have a lot of similarities, Tripp.
We can talk about a lot of things.
We could have been friends.
Tripp, you know a lot of people love you.
Alys visits you every day.
Secretly, without Auntie knowing.
And I know that even
if she doesn't tell me,
it hurts her to see you like this.
So please, wake up.
And by the way,
Alys broke up with me.
But I won't give up like before.
I'll wait for her.
What I'm asking from you is simple.
Tell me where you took him!
Okay, thank you.
What Dane?
Were you able to contact her?
Not yet.
Her phone is off.
Alys.
Come on, pick up.
MkvDrama.net